<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daftar Film</string>
    <string name="movie_judul">Movie Title</string>
    <string name="deskripsi">Description</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tv Show</string>

    <string-array name="data_judul">
        <item>Avenger: Invinity War</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Jurassic Galaxy</item>
        <item>Black Panther</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>Spiderman</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_judul2">
        <item>Justice League</item>
        <item>Widows</item>
        <item>Deep Blue Sea 2</item>
        <item>The Flash</item>
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Grey\'s Anatomy</item>
        <item>Marvel\'s Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D.</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Arctic</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rilis">
        <item>25 April 2018</item>
        <item>15 December 2018</item>
        <item>7 December 2018</item>
        <item>9 February 2018</item>
        <item>3 October 2018</item>
        <item>25 November 2018</item>
        <item>25 November 2018</item>
        <item>20 November 2018</item>
        <item>6 Desember 2018</item>
        <item>5 October 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rilis2">
        <item>23 Oktober 2018</item>
        <item>6 November 2018</item>
        <item>17 April 2018</item>
        <item>7 October 2014</item>
        <item>10 October 2012</item>
        <item>27 March 2005</item>
        <item>24 September 2013</item>
        <item>26 February 1986</item>
        <item>21 November 2018</item>
        <item>22 September 2014</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_skor">
        <item>8.3</item>
        <item>6.7</item>
        <item>5.8</item>
        <item>7.1</item>
        <item>8.1</item>
        <item>6.2</item>
        <item>6.3</item>
        <item>7.1</item>
        <item>6.8</item>
        <item>6.9</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_skor2">
        <item>6.3</item>
        <item>7.1</item>
        <item>8.0</item>
        <item>6.7</item>
        <item>5.8</item>
        <item>6.2</item>
        <item>6.8</item>
        <item>7.1</item>
        <item>8.1</item>
        <item>6.9</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_deskripsi">
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero
            to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal
            is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will
            on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and
            existence itself has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie,
            on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken.
            When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.
        </item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry
            King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world.
            Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orms half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.
        </item>
        <item>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys to save a boys life.
        </item>
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers and falls in love with struggling artist Ally. She has just about
            given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight.
        </item>
        <item>In the near future, a ship of space explorers crash land on an unknown planet. Theyre soon met with some of
            their worst fears as they discover the planet is inhabited by monstrous dinosaurs
        </item>
        <item>King T Challa returns home from America to the reclusive, technologically advanced African nation of Wakanda
            to serve as his countrys new leader. However, TChalla soon finds that he is challenged for the throne
        </item>
        <item>A war hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.
        </item>
        <item>Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a spider-man. When Wilson Kingpin
            Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.
        </item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of
            Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_deskripsi2">
        <item>Fuelled by his restored faith in humanity and inspired by Supermans selfless act, Bruce Wayne and Diana Prince
            assemble a team of metahumans consisting of Barry Allen, Arthur Curry and Victor Stone to face the catastrophic
            threat of Steppenwolf and the Parademons who are on the hunt for three Mother Boxes on Earth.
        </item>
        <item>A police shootout leaves four thieves dead during an explosive armed robbery attempt in Chicago. Their widows
            have nothing in common except a debt left behind by their spouses criminal activities. Hoping to forge a future
            on their own terms, they join forces to pull off a heist.
        </item>
        <item>When shark conservationist Dr. Misty Calhoun is invited to consult on a top secret project run by pharmaceutical
            billionaire Carl Durant, she is shocked to learn that the company is using unpredictable and highly aggressive bull
            sharks as its test subjects, which soon break loose and cause havoc.
        </item>
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning
            and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to
            move through Central City like an unseen guardian angel.
        </item>
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea.
            He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with
            a bow.
        </item>
        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle s Grey Sloan Memorial
            Hospital.
        </item>
        <item>Agent Phil Coulson of SHIELD Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division
            puts together a team of agents to investigate the new, the strange and the unknown around the globe,
            protecting the ordinary from the extraordinary.
        </item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Go ku.
            Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy
            was on his own, but easily managed.
        </item>
        <item>A man stranded in the Arctic is finally about to receive his long awaited rescue. However, after a
            tragic accident, his opportunity is lost and he must then decide whether to remain in the relative
            safety of his camp or embark on a deadly trek through the unknown for potential salvation.
        </item>
        <item>
            Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime worlds greatest foes, a man whose
            reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordons story and his rise from rookie
            detective to Police Commissioner
        </item>
    </string-array>



    <array name="data_foto">
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/7WsyChQLEftFiDOVTGkv3hFpyyt.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/fw02ONlDhrYjTSZV8XO6hhU3ds3.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/5Kg76ldv7VxeX9YlcQXiowHgdX6.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/to0spRl1CMDvyUbOnbb4fTk3VAd.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/wrFpXMNBRj2PBiN4Z5kix51XaIZ.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/uo7u2bRW6KPPe4ipTUqx5RZ9rwC.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/uxzzxijgPIY7slzFvMotPv8wjKA.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/AiRfixFcfTkNbn2A73qVJPlpkUo.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/iiZZdoQBEYBv6id8su7ImL0oCbD.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w1280/2uNW4WbgBXL25BAbXGLnLqX71Sw.jpg</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_foto2">
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9rtrRGeRnL0JKtu9IMBWsmlmmZz.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d31SGJSaX29ba5ZUbZcesGoDE7I.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xqjAHXMJLORx9vVsCTJ6ZPJcr3D.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185_and_h278_bestv2/fki3kBlwJzFp8QohL43g9ReV455.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185_and_h278_bestv2/mo0FP1GxOFZT4UDde7RFDz5APXF.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185_and_h278_bestv2/eqgIOObafPJitt8JNh1LuO2fvqu.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185_and_h278_bestv2/nv4nLXbDhcISPP8C1mgaxKU50KO.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185_and_h278_bestv2/3wx3EAMtqnbSLhGG8NrqXriCUIQ.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dxRc0Y4IjSRLC2fYaguXQtJCI4e.jpg</item>
        <item>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185_and_h278_bestv2/4XddcRDtnNjYmLRMYpbrhFxsbuq.jpg</item>
    </array>

    <string name="change_language_settings">change language settings</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
